Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/veronicachiaravalli-1861831b (LinkedIn) www.exponentialtechs.com (Company)

www.veronicachiaravalli.se/ronnie/ (Portfolio)

www.exponentialtechs.com/blog (Blog)

Top Skills

Web Design
Entrepreneurship
Social Media

Languages

Swedish (Full Professional)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)
Japanese (Limited Working)
French (Limited Working)
Italian (Limited Working)
English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Scrum Master Certification Specialization

Certified Artificial Intelligence Specialist

3D Content Creation for Virtual Reality

UX Design: 6 Paper Prototyping

Sketch for UX Design

Veronica Chiaravalli

Founder, CEO, CINO, CISO, CFO, & CRO | SpaceTech & Impact Entrepreneur | M. Azure AI Engineer | Frontend Dev. | Scrum Master | XR Designer | Innovator | Top Trainer | Advisory Board M. | Mentor @ CBS | Amb. ISS Labs

Stockholm

Summary

Emerging Technologies Sweden

Massive Transformative Purpose (MTP): The Moon, Mars, and Beyond – We Are Civilization Type One!: Leading Humanity Towards Accelerated Exponential Growth, Longevity, and Multi-planetary Exploration while Solving Social & Technological Impact Challenges with Converging Tech, Pioneering Innovation, & Research, Bringing Powerful Innovations to Market, & Building the Metaverse.

Veronica is a Visionary Entrepreneur & remote worker at heart that wears many different hats. By Visionary she means Steve Blank's definition: "Visionary entrepreneurs tend to see things. Where everybody sees noise, they see a pattern".

Advisor @ Lifeboat Foundation & Member of 3 Advisory Boards:

Space Settlement B.

Futurists B.

Media & Arts B.

She's a geek & loves accelerating technologies. In other words, she loves SPEED!

Member of the FutureFaster team - "The Future Is Faster Than You Think" (#1 bestseller - Amazon) by P. Diamandis & S. Kotler.

One of the Editors of "A Pioneer's Guide to Living on Mars" by P. Kokh.

World-Class Space Exec. Trainer & Speaker (Harv Eker A.).

Background:

Tech Entrepreneurship (Stanford U.)

Social Entrepreneurship Spec. Cert. (CBS)

IIEC B. S. Exec. Program C.

M. Azure Al Cert.

Al in Business Cert.

AI, Business & the Future of Work Cert.

Creativity & Al Spec. Cert. (TNS Parsons)

Technology Sales Cert. (U. of Maryland)

Facebook Social Media Mark. P. Cert.

Spark AR

Unity 3D Artist

Unity XR: How to Build AR & VR Apps. Spec. Cert.

Intro to VR Spec. (U. of London)

Extended Reality for Everybody Spec. (U. of Michigan)

Exec. D. Science Prof. Cert. (J. Hopkins U.)

Google Data Analyst Prof. Cert.

Google Analytics

Workshops:

Space Exp. & Space Missions

Space Entrep. & Business in Space

Clients:

Exponential Ent., Space Ent., Social Ent., Solopreneurs, the Fortune 500, & Investors.

Expertise:

Global Grand Challenges (GGC)

Innov. Solutions to Social & Tech. Global Impact

Int. Design for XR

Prof. AR Creator

UCI Training (Cert. 3D Artist)

Strategic Innov. Advice to Space & Cutting-Edge Startups

Strategic Foresight - Innovation & Space Projects

Pioneering Innov. & Research - Challenges in the New Space Ind.

World-Class Signature Training & Speaking

Executive, Entrepreneur, & Astronaut Live Virtual & Interactive Training

1-on-1 Transf. Business Coaching (Startups 1-5 years)

Pioneering Space Exploration & The New Era of Private Orbital Spaceflight Training

HCI & HRI: Cert. Robotics Educ. in MiRo & Parallax Cyber:bot

Partners:

Microsoft
Deep Knowledge Analytics
The Moon Society

Experience

Emerging Technologies Sweden - Space & Defence
Multi-planetary Innovator & Founder, CEO, CINO, CISO, CFO, and
CRO (Chief Robotics Officer)
May 2015 - Present (6 years 11 months)
SWEDEN/GLOBAL

- Officially started Emerging Technologies Sweden in June 2015 working with the gender gap and emerging and exponential tech, Business consulting company focusing on global grand challenges & global impact.
- CEO (Chief Executive Officer), CINO (Chief Innovation Officer), CISO (Chief Impact & Strategy Officer), CFO (Chief Futurist Officer), and CRO (Chief Robotics Officer).
- Successfully gave speeches at Purdue Univ. several times remotely.
- Delivered ExO Strategic Advice calls (advice, research, and keynote speech) to the startup ImmerseFX via OpenExo. Also worked on a project where I was interviewed (podcast and video) by Chris Parker from Ebullient.com.

Some Links:

https://www.openexo.com/ https://ebullient.com/podcast/veronicachiaravalli/

Career:

- Successfully finalized the IIEC Executive Programs (specialized in 5 Paths):
- 1) Emerging Technologies,
- 2) Exponential Technologies

- 3) Augmented Intelligence
- 4) Immersive Technologies
- 5) Robotics HRI & Human-Robotic Space Exploration.
- New Space Ind.: innovation management, research, lean start-up, bus. dev., emerging tech., and exponential tech., consulting services, prof. public speaking, and Emerg. and Exp. Tech. Training. Providing a UX, HCI, and human-robot int. (HRI) approach to the dev. of innovative services.
- Successfully Leading and designing social and space robotic workshops as a Robotics Educator and CRO (Chief Robotics Officer).
- Pattern recognition, planning, execution, & problem-solving. Leading projects from scratch to completion in a short time.

Cert. in The Process & Lifetime of a Space Mission (NASA), Inclusive Mindset (NASA), and in Found. for Excellence in Teaching Online (ASU). IIEC-Cert. CRO - HRI & Human-Robot Space Exploration.

Member of the Lifeboat Found. Advisory Board.

One of the editors of "A Pioneer's Guide To Living on Mars" and "Return to the Moon 7 - Proc. of the 2020 Lunar Dev. Conf.". Published articles at iotworlds.com.

Multiplanetary Space Exploration & Innovation - MSEI Founder, Global Exponential Innovator, Visionary Leader, and Owner of MSEI

February 2017 - Present (5 years 2 months)

Stockholm, Sweden

Website: http://www.exponentialtechs.com/space/agh/

- Founded my MSEI (startup) on 17/07/2017. Emerging Technologies Sweden is the present moving towards the future. MSEI is the future! They represent who I am, and who I am on my way to becoming.
- MSEI is an ExO in the development phase.

Title: Founder, Exponential Innovator, and Visionary Leader (working remotely). Head of HRI & Al Robotics (Space Industry).

- Hands-on experience working with innovation in the form of Space projects.
- Working with GGC (Global Grand Challenges) and Space challenges, applying a Human-Centered Design, Human-Computer Interaction Design, and Human-Robot Interaction Design approach.
- Working with pioneering innovation projects.

Gigstr

Designer, Developer, and Marketer January 2022 - Present (3 months)

Ongoing remote projects via Gigstr for different clients and industries. I recently joined and am part of several recruitment processes. Waiting for my first remote gigs via Gigstr.

I have never seen such an active company as Gigstr. They are fast and very effective. Gigstr is very open-minded and we hope that more companies will follow. Nowadays, it is very important to be able to work remotely and companies are not ready for sudden changes. Gigstr solves this gap and aligns with my way of thinking and working. Furthermore, for us remote workers, Gigstr opens up the doors and bridges the gap between candidates and companies. It also is a changemaker, something we really need in Sweden and the world.

The world is changing at an exponential speed and we are happy to be part of the changes that lead to a better world that gives everybody equal opportunities.

What I know as an Entrepreneur is that we live in the trillion-dollar gig economy! We raise the glass to Gigstr!

Remember: Innovation is not a straight line and there can be more than one way to solve a global challenge!

Millionaire Mind Online (MMO) Affiliate Marketer October 2021 - Present (6 months)

Affilate Marketer for MMO, promoting Harv Eker's digital products. Harv Eker is one of my Trainers. It is an honor!

Gathering the material and launching asap.

Taskflex Student Freelancer - Contract October 2021 - Present (6 months) Denmark

Freelance remote work via Taskflex based in Denmark. I offer online services as a Designer, Developer, and Marketer.

Taskflex is doing a great job in helping students get experience in different areas.

I am happy to have joined Taskflex-

Nowadays, we all know that the global market lacks roles for Junior Developers, Junior Designers, etc. I see that Taskflex has understood this gap very well. This indirectly targets the gender equality gap which I am very focused on solving as well. Companies do not understand that there is a huge danger in only publishing Senior roles because they make the gap even larger and create a negative impact overall. It is not a question of offering women education but also jobs. Both are equally important. Companies keep striving to spend less and get more. At the same time, big companies keep spending billions of dollars to solve the gender equality gap. There are 2 actions that are going in different directions. Diversity and inclusion are words that are being tossed around without understanding that it is very easy to fall into the trap of not being neither diverse nor inclusive. Only hiring Senior Designers and Senior Developers is NOT being neither inclusive nor diverse.

Copenhagen Business School Mentor October 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months) Denmark

- Finished the Social Entrepreneurship Specialization at Copenhagen Business School.
- Created project "Pioneering Innovation, Training, and Mentoring Program for Youngsters" to solve Covid-19 targeting the age groups 19 to 29 years of age.
- In 2022, I will be improving and launching the online coaching program. Aim: social impact.
- Mentoring social entrepreneurs to build social enterprises to fight COVID-19 (COVIDWISE) via Copenhagen Business School.

Explanation: "#covidWISE is an initiative funded by the Danish Innovation Foundation which supports social entrepreneurs with temporary business models, aimed at fighting the economic, social and health consequences of Covid-19."

- About Copenhagen Business University:
- "Centrally located in Copenhagen, the capital of Denmark, Copenhagen Business School (CBS) is one of the largest business schools in Europe with close to 23,000 students. CBS offers world-class research-based degree programs at undergraduate, graduate, and Ph.D. levels as well as executive and other post experience programs."

Website:

https://www.cbs.dk/en

The TOP Person - An International Business, Politics, and NGO Magazine and a Global Charity with HUB
The TOP Person Ambassador & Influencer
April 2021 - Present (1 year)

Sweden

- Successfully promoting the magazine as an Ambassador and Influencer.
- Supporting other Ambassadors.
- Sharing important events from my company that works with global grand challenges.

Cyber Security Forum Initiative
Graphic Designer
June 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 1 month)
Washington, D.C.

- Redesigned the CSFI website together with an international team remotely. Worked with web design, graphic design, prototypes, and WordPress CMS. See the link to the redesigned website below.
- Also volunteered for the CNPITH (The Center for Nonprofit Information Technology Hosting) where I was a member of, https://www.centerfornphosting.org/

Korpen Stockholm Water Gymnastics Instructor 2013 - 2015 (2 years) Stockholm

- Successfully trained more than 100 persons to lead a healthy life by training water gymnastics several times per week at Oasen Bad & Motion

Veronica & Staffan Webbdesign Freelance Web & Motion Graphics Designer 2013 - 2015 (2 years) Stockholm, Sweden

- Created WordPress CMS sites for restaurant business together with the Developer/Programmer Staffan Söderlind via Frilans Finans in independent projects. The work included graphic design and meetings with the customers.

SK Neptun - Water polo section Water polo trainer September 2014 - December 2014 (4 months)

Page 7 of 10

Stockholm

- Finalized the formal training as a Water Polo Instructor and trained youngsters with exercise on land and in the water.

Planet Fitness Water Gymnastics Instructor January 2013 - 2014 (1 year)

- Trained mixed groups of people in water gymnastics and created training programs.

More info at:

Vasastan

http://www.planetfitness.se/

SK Neptun

Swim Trainer and Synchro Swim Trainer at SK Neptun January 2013 - 2014 (1 year) Sthlm

- Successfully gave swimming lessons teaching the following levels: Baddaren, Hajen, Medley, Utmanaren, etc.
- Trained youngsters in Synchroteaching the following levels: Knattekonstsim, Knatte Fort., Level 1, Level 2, and eventually Bas.
- Learned how the synchro swimmers trained on land and in water.
- Learned technical expertise.

More information at:

http://www8.idrottonline.se/SKNeptun-Simidrott/

SSIF (Stockholm Studenters Idrottsförening) Swim Instructor / Swim Trainer January 2013 - 2014 (1 year)

- Successfully taught swimming courses: Crawl for adults.
- Learned how to teach adults with no previous experience in swimming.
- Learned how adults faced fear and other problems.

For more info see:

http://www.ssif.su.se/simning/

SS04

Swim Teacher

2013 - 2014 (1 year)

Stockholm

Teaching the following levels: Hajen and Fisken at SS04 (Solna Sundbyberg Simsällskap)..

My goal is to enter "Teknikskolan" at SS04 and work directly with groups that want to improve their technique in crawl, breaststroke, backstroke, and butterfly.

Feelgood

Water Gymnastics Instructor July 2012 - 2014 (2 years)

Grev Turegatan, Sthlm

Vattenhuset

Water Gymnastics/Swim/Baby Swim Instructor January 2012 - 2014 (2 years)

Water Gymnastics (in different levels), Baby Swim Instructor, and Swim Instructor. I did 3 practices (parallel): one as a Water Gymnastics Instructor (I obtained my Diploma), as a Swim Instructor (for children), and Baby Swim Instructor (for babies accompanied by their parents).

My experience in working for the Water House (Vattenhuset) taught me the learning process in babies, children, and adults. For me as a researcher and innovator it was a very important experience.

Grand Hotell Saltsjöbaden Water Gymnastics Instructor January 2013 - June 2013 (6 months) Saltsjöbaden

- Trained women in water gymnastics at Grand Hotell Saltsjöbaden.

Södertörns Simsällskap Swim Teacher August 2012 - December 2012 (5 months)

- Trained children swimming.
- Levels: Baddaren, Sköldpaddan, Fisken, etc.
- Worked with children from many backgrounds, saw them face fear of water, etc.

Medborgarskolan Group Leader 2009 - 2012 (3 years)

- Taught English to children and Spanish to adults.
- Successfully completed training from Medborgarskolan (courses on Pedagogy, etc).
- Prepared course material by myself and applied ideas.

Education

Copenhagen Business School

Social Entrepreneurship · (2021 - 2021)

Stanford University

Technology Entrepreneurship 1 - Stanford University + NovoEd · (2015 - 2015)

Rotterdam School of Management, Erasmus University

Innovation Management · (2021 - 2021)

SDA Bocconi

International Leadership and Organizational Behaviour · (2021 - 2021)

University of Maryland College Park

Entrepreneurship · (2021 - 2021)